<!DOCTYPE idea-plugin PUBLIC "Plugin/DTD" "http://plugins.intellij.net/plugin.dtd">
<idea-plugin>
    <name>ANTLRWorks</name>
    <id>ANTLRWorks</id>
    <version>1.2</version>
    <description>ANTLRWorks is a grammar development environment for ANTLR v3 grammars. It combines an excellent grammar-aware editor with an interpreter for rapid prototyping and a language-agnostic debugger for isolating grammar errors. ANTLRWorks helps eliminate grammar nondeterminisms, one of the most difficult problems for beginners and experts alike, by highlighting nondeterministic paths in the syntax diagram associated with a grammar. ANTLRWorks' goal is to make grammars more accessible to the average programmer, improve maintainability and readability of grammars by providing excellent grammar navigation and refactoring tools, and address the most common questions and problems encountered by grammar developers</description>

    <vendor url="http://www.antlr.org/works">ANTLR Project</vendor>

    <idea-version since-build="6197"/>

    <change-notes><![CDATA[
Version 1.2 - 08/31/2008<br>
<br>
Bug fix:<br>
    [AW-164] - Cannot paste text on the debugging input panel if grammar is read-only<br>
    [AW-177] - Cannot paste text into interpreter when file is read-only<br>
    [AW-121] - Remove ErrorListener from current thread<br>
    [AW-153] - Console of the current editor is not set when the frame is activated<br>
    [AW-155] - Remove prefs for last used symbol in debugger<br>
    [AW-162] - Quote a path with white space only on Windows when executing a shell command<br>
<br>
Improvement:<br>
    [AW-92] - Breakpoint per line and not only per rule as it is the case now<br>
    [AW-66] - Generate the code by default next to the grammar (see preferences)<br>
    [AW-141] - Ability to not display certain alert box<br>
    [AW-149] - Ability to disable the "Check Grammar" success dialog<br>
    [AW-154] - Full support for split grammar debug<br>
    [AW-156] - Support for custom file type in IntelliJ<br>
    [AW-158] - Rule name when exporting syntax diagrams<br>
    [AW-159] - Generated-code panel should synchronize when generated code changes on the disk<br>
    [AW-161] - Changed debugger port from 49153 (0xC001) to 49100<br>
    [AW-167] - Display optional alert if file is modified on the disk before reloading it<br>
    [AW-169] - Display alert when file content changed on the disk<br>
]]>
    </change-notes>

    <application-components>
        <component>
            <implementation-class>org.antlr.works.plugin.intellij.PIApplicationComponent</implementation-class>
        </component>
        <component>
            <implementation-class>org.antlr.works.plugin.intellij.PIEditorProvider</implementation-class>
        </component>
    </application-components>
</idea-plugin>